Frank Buxton Papers LSC.2380
UCLA Library Special Collections
Frank Buxton papers
1931-2008, undated
UCLA Library Special Collections
Buxton, Frank
LSC.2380
10.8 linear feet (13 boxes)
Frank Buxton was an actor, director, writer, host, and producer for assorted motion pictures and television programs. The collection consists of materials created and collected by Buxton related to the various projects he worked on throughout his career. The materials date from 1931 to 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9992394083606533
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Cynthia Sears, 2019 and 2022.
Biographical History
Frank Buxton (1930-2018) was an actor, director, writer, producer, and host for assorted motion pictures and television programs. During his career he worked on various productions including Discovery; The Odd Couple, Happy Days, Mork and Mindy, and Hot Dog.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of materials related to the career of film and television actor, producer, writer, host and director, Frank Buxton. The materials were created and collected by Buxton throughout his career, and offer insight into the workings of film and television productions. The collection mainly consists of original film and television scripts including Mork and Mindy, The Odd Couple, Happy Days, and Discovery. A small portion of the collection contains correspondence, notes, and assorted documents related to productions. The materials date from 1931 to 2008.
Television scripts; Screenplays; Actors -- United States -- Archives; Buxton, Frank -- Archives
- The Odd Couple: "Moonlighter" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Odd Couple: "Being Divorced is Never Having to Say I Do" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Odd Couple: "A Night to Dismember" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Odd Couple: "Shuffling off to Buffalo" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Odd Couple: "The Insomniac" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Odd Couple: "It's All Over Now, Baby Bird" script, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Odd Couple: "Vocal Girl Makes Good" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Odd Couple: "The Flying Felix" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Odd Couple: "The New Car" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Odd Couple: "Odd Decathlon" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Odd Couple: "Gloria Moves In" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Odd Couple: "The Odd Holiday" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Odd Couple: "That was no Lady" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Odd Couple: "Last Tango in Newark" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Odd Couple: "Where's Grandpa?" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Odd Couple: "Oscar's Promotion" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Odd Couple: "Partner's Investment" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Odd Couple: "You Saved My Life" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- The Odd Couple: "Does Your Mother Know You're Out, Rigoletto?" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- The Odd Couple: "You Saved My Life" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Odd Couple: "Partner's Investment" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Odd Couple: "Cleanliness is Next to Impossible" script, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The Odd Couple: "Mini-Story Lines" script, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- The Odd Couple: "Surprise! Surprise!" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- The Odd Couple: "The Fat Farm" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Chip 'N' Dale's Rescue Rangers: "A Creep in the Deep" script, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- The Odd Couple: "Felix's Wife's Boyfriend" script, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Odd Couple: "Psychic, Shmycic" script, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Young and the Restless: "#4048" script, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- The Young and the Restless: "#4049" script, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- This is Your Life 30th Anniversary Special script, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
- Happy Days: "Dance Contest" script, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Happy Days: "Open House" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Happy Days: "Give the Band a Hand" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Happy Days: "Fonzie Joins the Band" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Happy Days: "Richie's Car" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Happy Days: "Motorcycle" script, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Happy Days: "Richie Moves Out" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Happy Days: "Fonzie's Getting Married" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Happy Days: "Fonzie Moves In" script, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Happy Days: "Jailhouse Rock" script, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- One Day at a Time: "Jealousy" script, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Happy Days: "Beauty Contest" script, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Happy Days: "A Star is Bored" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Happy Days: "Wish Upon a Star" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Happy Days: "Big Money" script, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Superior Court: "Polygamy" script, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- A Night in Casablanca script, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- The Beach Brothers: "Home is Where the Heart Is" script, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Go West script, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Divorce Court script, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Calucci's Department script, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Roll Out!: "Pilot" script, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- MASH: "Divided We Stand" script, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Dominic's Dream: "Pilot" script, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Beach Brothers call sheet, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Roll Out! correspondence, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Research by Guilbert Banks, Jr., undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Diana Rigg Show: "Take My Sister" script, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- MASH: "5 O'Clock Charlie" script, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Beaches script, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- The Young and the Restless: "#4047" script, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- The Odd Couple: "The Hustler" script, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- The Odd Couple: "The First Baby" script, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
- The Odd Couple: "I'm Dying of Unger" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- The Odd Couple: "The Pen is Mightier than the Pencil" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Frog script, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- The Odd Couple: "Myrna's Debut" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4, 6)
- Umpire script, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- The Odd Couple: "The Princess" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- The Odd Couple: "Big Mouth" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- The Odd Couple: "The Murray Who Came to Dinner" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- The Odd Couple: "Odd Father" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- The Odd Couple: "Take My Furniture, Please" script, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- The Odd Couple: "The Odyssey Couple" script, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
- The Odd Couple: "Don't Believe in Roomers" script, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- The Odd Couple assorted material, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Chad Hanna script, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- The Little Colonel script, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Bright Eyes script, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- The Jack Benny Television Program: "Jack Locked in Tower of London" script, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- David Harum script, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Sunday Funnies script, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1-2, 4)
- Johnny Got His Gun script, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Emo Philips assorted material, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- World's Greatest Dad script, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Mork and Mindy: "Mork's First Christmas" script, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- MASH: "Bombshells" script, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- The Happy Days: "Pilot" script, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Mork and Mindy: "Sky Flakes Keep Falling on My Head" script, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Mork and Mindy: "Old Fears" script, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Mork and Mindy: "The Night They Raided Mind-Ski's" script, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Mork and Mindy: "Mama Mork, Papa Mindy" script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
- Mork and Mindy: "Rich Mork, Poor Mork" script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
- Mork and Mindy: "My Dad Can't Beat Up Anybody" script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
- Mork and Mindy: "Long Before We Met..." script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Mork and Mindy: "Alienation" script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Mork and Mindy: "Pajama Game II" script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Mork and Mindy: "P.S. 2001" script, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- The Odd Couple: "I Gotta Be Me" script, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- The Odd Couple: "Schizocleania" script, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11-15)
- Unnamed scripts and notes, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- The Odd Couple assorted material, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- The Odd Couple: "The Ides of April" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
- The Odd Couple: "The Odd Couples" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
- The Odd Couple: "Sometimes a Great Ocean" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8-10, 12)
- The Odd Couple: "Closely Watched Strains" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- The Odd Couple: "My Strife in Court" script, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- The Odd Couple: "Big Mouth" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- The Odd Couple: "The Princess" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- The Odd Couple: "The Murray Who Came to Dinner" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- The Odd Couple: "The Odd Monks" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- The Odd Couple: "Felix's First Commercial" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- The Odd Couple: "Gloria, Hallelujah" script, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- The Odd Couple: "Mini-Story Lines" script, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- The Odd Couple: "That's Entertainment?" script, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- The Odd Couple: "Break Up the Band... or Else" script, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- The Odd Couple: "Our Fathers" script, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- The Odd Couple: "Old Flames Never Die" script, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- The Odd Couple: "Oscar Remarries" script, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Love, American Style: "Blackouts" script, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Love, American Style: "Love and the Impressionist" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Love, American Style: "The Happy Days" script, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- The Many Loves of Dobie Gillis: "Love is a Science" script, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Out-of-Towners: "Teaser" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Love, American Style: "Love and Dear Old Dad and Mom" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Love, American Style: "There's No Job Like No Job" script, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- No Man's Valley script, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- The Johnsons Are Home script, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "The Longest Hook Shot in the World" script, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "The Bill Cosby Special" script, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "Growing, Growing, Grown" script, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "Buck Buck" script, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "Street Football" script, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- The Kraft Music Hall: "Jack Benny - Fiddler on the Loose" script, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Robin Hood: "When Things Were Rotten" script, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Johnny Got His Gun script, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Tony Marko: "Pilot" script, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Cops script, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "The Regular Way" script, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- I Spy: "The Sparrowhawk" script, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- The Dick Van Dyke Show: "Honeymoons are for the Lucky" script, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- The Bill Cosby Show: "The Second Bill Cosby Special" script, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The Dick Van Dyke Show: "Go Tell the Birds and the Bees" script, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The Bob Newhart Show: "I Want to be Alone" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- The Bob Newhart Show: "Don't go to Bed Mad" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Sanford and Son: "A House is not a Poolroom" script, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Sanford and Son: "Superflyer" script, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- One Day at a Time: "How to Succeed Without Trying" script, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Skid Row script, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- The Picasso Summer script, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Wives: "Pilot" script, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- The Barbara Eden Show: "Teaser" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- The Bob Newhart Show: "Mom, I L-L-Love You" script, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- The Effects of Communicator Incompatibility on Children's Judgments of Television Programs report, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Beyond the Moon" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "How to Train a Puppy" script, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Hamsters, Guinea Pigs and Mice" script, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "How They Named the Stars" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Giant Mammals" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "The Carnival of Animals" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Prehistoric Man" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Benjamin Franklin" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Galileo" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Discovery Visits Rome" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Colonial Williamsburg" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Numbers" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Fact, Fancy and Freedom" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Sing-A-Song of Politics" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "The Other Side of the Screen" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "The World of Mark Twain" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Flying Through the Air" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Explorers Before Columbus" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "More About Dinosaurs" script, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to the Republican Convention" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Discovery Interview with General Dwight D. Eisenhower" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Interview with Senators Hubert Humphrey and Sam J. Ervin" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to the Democratic Convention" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
- Discovery: "Fact, Fancy and Freedom" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Mummies & Pyramids" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Strange Pets" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Jars, Mirrors and Window Panes" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Statue of Liberty" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Thomas Alva Edison" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Abraham Lincoln" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "We Love You" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "Arms and Armor" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "What Makes You Tick - the Human Heart" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "How Hot is Hot?" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "George Washington" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "When Mommy and Daddy Were Young - III" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "Nocturnal Animals" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Transatlantic Jet" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Galileo" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Benjamin Franklin" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Prehistoric Man" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "The Carnival of Animals" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Hawaii - the Newest State" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Origami" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Discovery: "Folk Song of History" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Discovery: "The Foo Esing Theatre (Chinese Children's Theatre)" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Discovery: "Giant Mammals" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Discovery: "This is Discovery" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Discovery: "Unseen World" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Discovery: "Chinese New Year" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Discovery: "Where do Words Come From?" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "Animal Homes" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "More About Dinosaurs" script, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "How They Named the Stars" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "Statue of Liberty" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "Beyond the Moon" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "The Sun" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "Mythology" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "Discovery Visits Rome" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "Mummies & Pyramids" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "Strange Pets" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "Jars, Mirrors and Window Panes" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "How Does Your Garden Grow?" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "The Human Body" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Discovery: "Picture Writing" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Discovery: "Primitive Music" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Discovery: "Reaching for the Moon" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Discovery: "The Weird World of Witchcraft" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Discovery: "The Election of the President" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Discovery: "Heroes of the Wild West" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Discovery: "It All Adds up to You" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Discovery: "The Wondrous World of Mythology" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Discovery: "What's Funny?" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Discovery: "The Human Brain" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Discovery: "Foreign Correspondent" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Discovery: "Liverpool: The Base of the Beat" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Discovery: "When Mom and Dad were Young - the 40's" script, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Discovery: "Discovery Visits the Baird Marionettes" script, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Discovery: "Surprises and Disguises" script, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Discovery: "All About Snakes" script, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "The Plains Indians" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Looking at the Stars" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Forest Indians" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Fun on Skis" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Air and Air Pressures" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Corpuscle and His Friends" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Numbers" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Discovery: "Colonial Williamsburg" script, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Live From Planet Earth script, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
- Frankie and Johnny script, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Miracle at Springhill Mine script, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- The Lucille Ball - Desi Arnaz Hour Show: "Lucy Hunts Uranium" script, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- I Love Lucy: "The Ricardos Dedicate a Statue" script, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- I Accuse script, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- The District: "To Serve and Protect" script, undated (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
- What's In? script, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- TV Guide Award Show, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 5, 8)
- Get the Message: "Pilot" script, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- It's a Joke, Son! script, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- The Diary of Ellen Rimbauer script, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Amos 'N' Andy: "T.V. Script #1" script, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
- The Bishop's Wife script, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Amos 'N' Andy: "Hospitalization Policy" script, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- The Red Skelton Show: "The Medicine Man" script, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- The Red Skelton Show: "The Mark of Zero" script, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Li'l Abner script, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- A Prairie Home Companion script, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
- Crazy in Love script, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- My Shadow script, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
- A Day at the Circus script, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Horse Feathers script, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
- A-N-I-M-A-L C-R-A-C-K-E-R-S script, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
- At Long Last Leo script, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Discovery: "Man From Pisa" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Israel" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Three Young Lives for Kenya" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Greece" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Athens" script, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Japan" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to West Berlin" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Greece" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Athens" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to School in London" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Hawaii" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Dolphins" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "The Golden Invasion" script, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "The American Cowboy" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "The Whaling Years" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Discovery Visits the Baird Marionettes" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "The Plains Indians" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Alaska" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "The Funny History of the Horseless Carriage" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Discovery: "Discovery Goes to Alaska" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
- Discovery: "Yuri and Irina Come to America" script, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "Flying Like a Bird" script, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "Music and Rhythm" script, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "How Animals Talk" script, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Discovery: "How to Pick a Puppy" script, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Hot and Cold and in Between" script, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "The World You Can't See!" script, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Transatlantic Jet" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Nocturnal Animals" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "The Desert People" script, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "The Inverted Amphitheater" script, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Discovery: "Forest Indians" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "The Plains Indians" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "The Strangest Fish of All" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Desert Animals - II" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Music Boxes" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "The Funniest Fellow in the Zoo" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Trip to the Moon IV - The Astronauts" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "Primitive Music" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Discovery: "We Love You" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "What Makes You Tick -- the Human Heart" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Air and Air Pressure" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Unseen World" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Discovery Looks at Washington - Part II" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Measuring Things" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Discovery: "Water" script, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Limelight script, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- The Odd Couple: "The Big Broadcast" script, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
- The Odd Couple: "Password" script, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
- Happy Days: Concepts, Scripts, Stories & Notions for 1974-75 Season (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Happy Days: "Goin' to Chicago" script, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
- Happy Days: "Howard's 45th Fiasco" script, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
- Happy Days: "Not With My Sister, You Don't" script, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)